Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Office of the Dean of Students Records, 1915-2012
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1915-2010, UWM Archival Collection 48; 19 cubic ft. (23 boxes) 5 digital text files (2 MB)
  - Suave (Bourgeois of Suave Intellect), 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 119)
  - Sufi Dancing, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Suhkha/Duhkha, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 120)
  - Sun, 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 121)
  - Sun Party, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Sunny Goodstreet Film Society, 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Surprise Party, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 122)
  - Switchboard, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Symphonic Band, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Symphony Orchestra at UWM, 1959-1982 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - T'ai Chi Chuan Club, 1974-1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - T'ai Chi Club, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Tae Kwon Do Association, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 123)
  - Tae Kwon Do Club, 1977-1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Tai Ju Body Sense, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 124)
  - Tailgunners at UWM, 1992-1994 (Box 19, Folder 125)
  - Taiwanese Student Association, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Talent, Inc. Talisman, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Tamal Students Association, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 126)
  - Target Medical Doctor Association, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 127)
  - TASK [Teamwork and Student Knowledge], 1969 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Task Force for Implementation of Student Disciplinary Guidelines on UWM Campus, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Task Force on the Status of Women in Student Affairs at UWM, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Tau Kappa Epsilon, 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Tau Omega, 1967-1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Tax Association, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 128)
  - Tea Totallers Social Club, 1975-1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Teaching of the Ascended Masters, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Tempest/Cheshire Literary Magazine
    - 1957-1974 (Box 8, Folder 13-14)
    - Activities, 1962-1971 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Financial Records, 1969-1973 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Tenant Resource Organization, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Tennessee Jed's Film Society, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Terminal Velocity, Airbourne Activities, and Skydiving Club, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 129)
  - Termpaper Companies, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Thai Association, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Theatre Etc., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Theatre Student Association, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Theta Phi Mu, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Theta Sigma Phi, 1966-1971 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Theta Sigma Upsilon, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Theta Xi, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Third Coast Design Coop, 1983-1987 (Box 19, Folder 130)
  - Third Coast Group, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Third World Tuju Club, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - TKB Social Club, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 131)
  - Today's Special, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 132)
  - Tony Earl for Governor Campaign, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Travel Club at UWM, 1991-1994 (Box 19, Folder 133)
  - Tri Sigma, 1949-1967 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Triangle Fraternity, 1961-1963 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Triathlon Club, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Truth Encounter, 1977-1982 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Tupperware Party, 1972-1975 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Turkish Student Association, 1977-1988 (Box 19, Folder 134)
  - U. S.-China People's Friendship Association, 1978-1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - U. S. Committee for Justice to Latin American Political Prisoners, 1975-1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - U. S. Labor Party, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - U. S. Tamburello Sport Club, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 153)
  - Udall for President, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - U-Fest, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Ukrainian Club, 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Ultimate Club, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 135)
  - Unification Church, 1974-1980 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Union Employees Association, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 136)
  - Union for Democratic Socialism, 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Union for Social Action, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Union of Progressive Student Media, 1988-1990 (Box 19, Folder 137)
  - Union of Progressive Students, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Union Vodvil, 1920-1921 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - United Black Student Front, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - United Campus Christian Fellowship, 1960-1967 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - United Crafts Center, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - United Farmworkers Support Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - United Gay Students at UWM, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - United Greek Council at UWM, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 138)
  - United Greek Letter Organization Council, 1982-1985 (Box 19, Folder 139)
  - United Ministry in Higher Education, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - United Student Alliance
    - 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - 1980-1985 (Box 19, Folder 140)
  - United Student Fellowship, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - United Student Sociological Society, 1982-1985 (Box 19, Folder 141)
  - United Students' Alliance at UWM, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 142)
  - United Students Coalition, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - United We Stand for America, UWM Chapter, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 143)
  - Unity, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 144)
  - University Aquarium Club, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 145)
  - University Brass Ensemble, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - University Bridge Club, 1979-1990 (Box 19, Folder 146)
  - University Civil Liberties Union, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - University Committee Against the Draft, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - University Committee to Save North Division High School, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - University Democratic Alliance, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - University Forum Organization, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - University Marketing, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 147)
  - University Players, 1957-1971 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - University Political Action Council, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - University Productions, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 148)
  - University Religious Council, 1954-1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - University Scottish Society, 1969-1971 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - University Ski Team, 1988-1992 (Box 19, Folder 149)
  - University Student Government, 1956-1974 (Box 8, Folder 56-64)
  - University Student Services Award, 1980-1993 (Box 21, Folder 2-4)
  - University Students' Committee, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - University Symphony Orchestra, 1957-1963 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - University Typing Services, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - University Velo Club, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - University Wheelmen, 1975-1992 (Box 19, Folder 150)
  - University Women's Council, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Unix Bombsquad, 1982-1993 (Box 19, Folder 151)
  - The Unnamed Social Club, 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Upward Bound, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Urban Planning Students Organization, 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Urban Social Institutions Student Organization, 1982-1990 (Box 19, Folder 152)
  - Urban Studies Club, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - US, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 154)
  - Users of IBM/PS 2, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 155)
  - Using Union Policies Better for Students, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 156)
  - UW-Milwaukee Winds, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - UWM Anti-War Committee, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - UWM Blood Donors Club, 1971-1976 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - UWM Cheerleaders, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - UWM Climbing Club, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - UWM College Democrats, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - UWM Community Vietnam Moratorium Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - UWM Company, Association of the United States Army, 1969-1976 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - UWM Concert Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - UWM Flying Club, 1966-1986 (Box 19, Folder 157)
  - UWM Folk Music Club, 1966-1976 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - UWM Frisbee Club, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - UWM Hart for Governor Committee, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - UWM-Libertarian Party, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - UWM March of Dimes, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - UWM Mett Organization, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - UWM-NAACP, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - UWM National Student Organizations Projects Committee, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - UWM Olympic Freestyle Wrestling Club, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - UWM Panther Cheerleaders, 1959-1976 (Box 19, Folder 158)
  - UWM Panther Pack, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - UWM Post, 1957-1969 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - UWM Pre-Vet Medicine Club, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - UWM Real Estate Club, 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - UWM Self Defense Association, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - UWM Student Broadcast Club, 1967-1971 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - UWM Students for Gene McCarthy, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - UWM Students for Humphrey, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - UWM Wargaming Club, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - UWWC Alumni Association at UWM, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Varsity Club, 1957-1978 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Varsity Publications, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 159)
  - VCR Club, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Vegetarian Society of UWM, 1989-1993 (Box 19, Folder 160)
  - Venture Capitalists of UWM, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 161)
  - Veterans' Advocate, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 162)
  - Veterans Club
    - 1957-1959 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - 1957-1990 (Box 19, Folder 163)
  - Veteran's Party of UWM, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Vicious Circle, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War, 1977-1983 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Visions 90, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 164)
  - Visual Educators Alliance, 1992-1994 (Box 19, Folder 165)
  - Vitagraph Film Society, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Voice, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 166)
  - Voice for Choice, 1992-1994 (Box 19, Folder 167)
  - Volunteer Services Unlimited, 1965-1972 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Volunteers in Service to America, 1965-1968 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Way Campus Outreach, 1975-1985 (Box 19, Folder 168)
  - We the People, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 169)
  - Wednesday Afternoon Group Experience, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Wesley Foundation
    - 1958-1963 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - 1961-1968 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Wholistic Health Organization, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Wild Party, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 170)
  - Winter Carnival, 1963-1968 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Winterim, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - WIRS (Wisconsin Independent Radio Station), 1981 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Wisconsin Adventurers, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Wisconsin Alliance, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Wisconsin Amnesty Center, 1975-1980 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Wisconsin Art Therapy Association, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Wisconsin Citizens for SALT, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Wisconsin Civil Liberties Union, UWM Chapter, 1977-1980 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Wisconsin Committee Against the Draft, 1980-1984 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Wisconsin NORML, 1976-1984 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Wisconsin Public Interest Research Group, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Wisconsin Society for Psychical Research Student Associates, 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Wisconsin Student Foresters, 1962-1964 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Wisconsin Veteran's Rights Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Wisconsin Veterans Union, 1972-1987 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Wisconsin Voice of Christian Youth, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Wisconsin Youth Coalition for Muskie, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Women and Architecture, 1983-1988 (Box 19, Folder 171)
  - Women for Wood, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Women in Communication, Inc., 1977-1991 (Box 19, Folder 172)
  - Women Writers' Collective, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Women's Association, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 173)
  - Women's Athletic Association, 1940, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Women's Chorus, 1957-1965 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Women's Health Coalition, 1978-1983 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Women's Liberation, 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Women's Recreation Association, 1957-1967 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Women's Softball Club at UWM, 1989-1994 (Box 19, Folder 174)
  - Work Incentive Training Program, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - World Affairs Research Society, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - World Congress at UWM, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - World Federalist Association at UWM, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 175)
  - World Perspective at UWM, 1991-1995 (Box 19, Folder 176)
  - World Portrait, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 177)
  - Writer's Block, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 178)
  - Writers Guild, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Wye Knott Party, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 179)
  - Xanadu Film Society, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Y.W.C.A., undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Yavneh, 1963-1966 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Yoga and Meditation Center, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 180)
  - Yoga Society, 1973-1980 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - You Make a Difference (UMAD), 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 181)
  - You've Got a Friend at UWM, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Young Adult United Methodists, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 182)
  - Young Adults, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 183)
  - Young Americans for Freedom, 1966-1972 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Young Communist League, 1970-1985 (Box 19, Folder 184)
  - Young Democrats, 1957-1963 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Young Executives, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 185)
  - Young Libertarian Alliance, 1980-1991 (Box 19, Folder 186)
  - Young Republicans, 1957-1966 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Young Socialist Alliance Club, 1969-1982 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Young Socialist Association, 1985-1989 (Box 19, Folder 187)
  - Young Socialist Campaign Committee, 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Young Socialists, 1958-1980 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Young Socialists for Camejo and Reid, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Young Socialists for Jenness and Pulley, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Young Socialists for Pulley and Zimmer, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Young Socialists for SA, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Your Dates, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 188)
  - Youth for Bayh Committee, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Youth International Party, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - YSU Film Society, 1975-1984 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - YWCA, Student Chapter, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 189)
  - Zephyr Party, 1976-1982 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Zero Credit, 1988-1992 (Box 19, Folder 190)
  - Zero Population Growth, 1971-1975 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Zeta Beta Tau
    - 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 19-20)
    - 1967-1973 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Zeta Sigma Chi, 1990-1992 (Box 19, Folder 191)
  - Zeta Zeta Xi Sorority, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 192)
  - Zeta Zeta Zeta, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Zoology Club, 1974-1980 (Box 9, Folder 87)
- Subject Files, 1970-2009, Accession 2010-069; 10 cubic ft. (10 boxes); Additions of subject files dating from circa 1970 to 2009. Records largely concern the Office of Student Life's interaction with the Student Association, including arbitration between students, responses to student initiatives, and settlement of SA controversies. The materials only cover those cases in which the Dean of Students was directly involved. Also included in the accession are files relating to the general operation of the Office of Student Life, including audits and annual reports.